

Jared M. Haggit
Sr. Product Designer

About Me

Design professional with 6+ years of experience creating user-centric, visually appealing, and high-performing web and mobile experiences. I solve problems with data at the intersection of business viability, customer usability, and technical feasibility.

Contact

614.596.5653

Jmhaggit@gmail.com

References

Dr. Charles Matthews

Professor of Entrepreneurship, University of Cincinnati

Charles.matthews@uc.edu

Experience

Product Designer II

Apr. 2023 - Present

PNC Bank

- Envisioned, planned, and designed 7 features for PNC's new mobile app
- Created interactive prototypes and wireframes in Sketch and Invision to convey design concepts and user flows
- Created and managed design system components, guidelines and assets for PNCs new mobile banking design system
- Collaborated closely with product managers, developers, and executives to balance business objectives with user goals

Sr. Product Designer

Jun. 2022 - Apr. 2023

GE Aviation

- Led the redesign of the platform search experience for over 100,000 users worldwide; decreasing, on average, time on task by 34.2% and increasing overall satisfaction.
- Collaborated closely with a senior development manager and 6 engineers to design, validate and implement platform search improvements

Product Designer

Mar. 2021 - May 2022

Battleface Inc.

- Improved UK quote conversion by 13.2%
- Planned, moderated, and synthesized 40+ exploratory research interviews which led to a 7.69% increase in US conversion
- Owned the end-to-end design process as the first product design hire in the US
- Led implementation of Figma, Userinterviews, Hotjar, Otter.ai and Dovetai

Education

User Experience Design

2017

General Assembly

Bachelor of Arts

2010 - 2015

University of Cincinnati

Tools

Figma, Sketch, Invision, Userzoom, Hotjar, Userinterviews, Miro, Mural, & Amplitude